likelovequotes.com 2015-12-22

# Privacy Policy | LikeLoveQuotes.com

**LikeLoveQuotes.Com Privacy Policy**

LikeLoveQuotes.Com respects your right to the privacy of the personal information you provide us. To that end, unless otherwise indicated, any personal information you provide to LikeLoveQuotes.Com will be known only to two parties: you and LikeLoveQuotes.Com. The following policy explains how your personal information will be treated as you use our sites and features. Personal information means your name, street and e-mail addresses, billing information, click-through activity and any other personal information you may provide here. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.

**Traffic data**

Each time a visitor comes to a LikeLoveQuotes.Com, our servers — like most on the Web — collect some basic technical information, including, for example, the visitor’s domain name (e.g., whether the user is logged on from aol.com or whitehouse.gov), referral data (e.g., we record the address of the last URL a user visited prior to clicking through to a Lessons Learned In Life site) and browser and platform type (e.g., a Safari browser on a Mac platform).

We also count, track and aggregate the visitor’s activity into our analysis of general traffic flows at our sites (e.g. tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows within the LikeLoveQuotes.Com sites, etc.). We may merge information about visitors and visits into group data, which may then be shared on an aggregated basis with our business partners; but we will not disclose your individual identity or personally identifiable data without your permission. When we do present aggregated information to outside companies, no one will be able to identify you or contact you.

**Use of cookies**

A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies in a limited way to help deliver advertisements, to identify unique browsers that visit us and to track usage throughout our site. The information about readership and site usage that LikeLoveQuotes.Com collects through cookies is aggregated into general reports about readership and not tied to individual identities.

**Membership**

LikeLoveQuotes.Com members provide us with personal information including their name and email address. LikeLoveQuotes.Com keeps all such information strictly confidential and does not reuse, resell or redistribute it in any way.

At the time of registering for membership, LikeLoveQuotes.Com members are asked whether they wish to receive e-mail from LikeLoveQuotes.Com of notification to alerts of our latest post. LikeLoveQuotes.Com does not reuse or resell the list of users who have “opted in” to such mailings, and users are able to opt-out of receiving future emails by “unsubscribing” to the email (found on bottom of email)

**“Sharing” feature**

LikeLoveQuotes.Com offers a “share” feature, allowing site visitors to share content with friends via Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, Google, Email, and many more to inform them about content they might be interested in seeing. For this feature to function, we ask for e-mail addresses for the recipient (so we know who to mail the message to) and from the sender (so we can tell the recipient who sent the e-mail). We do not store or save these addresses and you will not receive e-mail or other communications from LikeLoveQuotes.Com or its partners as a result of having used this feature.

“Sharing” includes a mail service that individual visitors to LikeLoveQuotes.Com use to send individual e-mails. While this tool cannot be used to send mass “spam” mailings, LikeLoveQuotes.Com has no control over how our visitors use it, and any e-mail sent through it originates with, and is the responsibility of, the sender, not LikeLoveQuotes.Com

**Promotion**

From time to time LikeLoveQuotes.Com, may in the future, sponsor sweepstakes, contests or other events, which require the collection, processing and storage of individual contact and demographic information (e.g., your age and state of residence) to be used for the event. LikeLoveQuotes.Com may also co-sponsor these events along with other companies, in which case the user’s individual contact and demographic information is likely to be shared with other participating sponsors, who may use this information as they wish. A registrant’s personal contact and demographic information will not be released to any third-party organization other than named sponsors without the user’s consent, and LikeLoveQuotes.Com will request that such named sponsors uphold the privacy of the registrants’ information by not distributing or sharing such information with any other businesses or organizations.

**Surveys**

LikeLoveQuotes.Com will from time to time conduct voluntary surveys of visitors to the site to obtain aggregate demographic information about them. Such information may be compiled and shared in the aggregate with business partners and other third parties, but no personal details will be traceable or associated with specific individuals.

**Our commitment to children’s privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is important to us. For that reason, we do not collect or maintain information at our Web sites from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our Web site is structured to attract anyone under 13.

**Other disclosure of personal information**

LikeLoveQuotes.Com will not otherwise use or disclose your personal information (personally identifiable data such as your name, email address, password) without your consent except (i) as described in this privacy policy, or (ii) as required by law to be disclosed. This policy does not protect information you post to any on-line bulletin board, chat room, newsgroup or other public forum within our Web sites.

**Unsubscribe and data removal policies**

If you would like to remove your name and e-mail address from our LikeLoveQuotes.Com registration database, please use/click the unsubscribe link in your email which is located at the bottom of every LikeLoveQuotes.Com notification.

**Other sites**

LikeLoveQuotes.Com in the future, may contain links to other sites on the Web. We cannot control and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other Web sites.

**Who can I ask if I have any additional questions?**

If you have any further questions or concerns about LikeLoveQuotes.Com’s privacy policies and use of personal information, please send them to info at LikeLoveQuotes dot Com

### Got Something to Say! Comment below :-

comments
